<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hadi Sandid</title><link>https://hsandid.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Hadi Sandid</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 18:36:23 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hsandid.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Adding Custom Instructions to the RISC-V GNU-GCC toolchain</title><link>https://hsandid.github.io/posts/risc-v-custom-instruction/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 18:36:23 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://hsandid.github.io/posts/risc-v-custom-instruction/</guid><description>This tutorial is an updated version of Nitish Srivastava&amp;rsquo;s tutorial Adding custom instruction to RISCV ISA and running it on gem5 and spike. I&amp;rsquo;ve also used some tips Jim Wilson gave on the following mailing list. Installing the RISC-V GNU/GCC toolchain We will be building the RISC-V GNU/GCC RV64GC Newlib Cross-compiler on an Ubuntu machine. If you&amp;rsquo;d like to use another configuration; you can check the repository instructions here.</description></item><item><title>Source Engine &amp; Game Design</title><link>https://hsandid.github.io/posts/game-dev/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 18:36:23 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://hsandid.github.io/posts/game-dev/</guid><description>Game design has been one of my favourite hobbies since High School.
While I lacked skills in the field of programming or 2D/3D design at the start, I have been slowly making it up over the years by learning to use some popular tools.
These tools include :
Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator (2D and 3D design) Visual Studio Code (C++ Programming) I have mainly used the Source Engine (tm) , which is a 3D engine developed by Valve Software, to bring my works to life.</description></item><item><title>Hiking around Lebanon</title><link>https://hsandid.github.io/posts/hiking-around-lebanon-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 18:36:23 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://hsandid.github.io/posts/hiking-around-lebanon-2/</guid><description>Baadaran Throughout our hike in Baadaran, we walked alongside a local river and through some open areas and villages with great views. Barouk On our hike through Barouk, we visited a local water source and an abandoned landing strip, which gave us a good view on all surrounding villages.</description></item><item><title>Hiking around Lebanon</title><link>https://hsandid.github.io/posts/hiking-around-lebanon-3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 18:36:23 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://hsandid.github.io/posts/hiking-around-lebanon-3/</guid><description>Nahr Ej Jahliye For this hike, we walked alongside a well-maintained trail alongside a local river. We also visited a small village with very friendly locals. Jisr El Qadi We scaled down the side of a mountain for the majority of this hike, before arriving at a river with several waterfalls</description></item><item><title>Hiking around Lebanon</title><link>https://hsandid.github.io/posts/hiking-around-lebanon-4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 18:36:23 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://hsandid.github.io/posts/hiking-around-lebanon-4/</guid><description>Mazraat El Daher The village of Mazraat El Daher is very close to my hometown Ez-Zaarouriye. We want on a small hike there, visiting an old church along the way, and sitting down at a small cafe to enjoy the view from there Baakleen We hiked alongside the local river, and visited restaurants such as "Challalat Al Zarka" where you could eat next to waterfalls. Bisri River Many remnants of the Roman empire stills stand alongside the Bisri river.</description></item><item><title>Hiking around Lebanon</title><link>https://hsandid.github.io/posts/hiking-around-lebanon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 18:36:23 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://hsandid.github.io/posts/hiking-around-lebanon/</guid><description>In my free time, I like to go hiking with friends around lebanon. Here are some of the hikes I’ve participated in : Ehden Ehden is a very touristic area in the North of Lebanon, and offers some several hiking trails which are maintained by local guides. Kaftoun Kaftoun is another area in the North of Lebanon. On our hike through the region we walked alongside a river, and visited a local covent.</description></item></channel></rss>